Let's be president
four times president CR and eight times
MDRT. In 2025 alone she achieved more
than 1 million a people around
over the past decade she has helped more
than thousand individual and families
secure their financial future through
their dedication and passion.
Huganai also known as Jojo is an Islamic
financial planner and he has achieved
nine times MDRT premier MDA and is a
potential NDRT ambassador.
Since joining us in year 2010, Jojo has
served more than 2,500 customers helping
them to fulfill their profession and
life aspirations.
Thanks. Gaga and Jojo have been amazing
role models for everyone here. Before we
dive in, tell us one word that best
describe your credential journey so far.
>> So I start first. Yeah. Okay. So my the
one word that actually to describe my
credential journey is transformation.
Anyone of you can relate to me
transformation.
And why I say this actually I truly
believe that transformation is very
important to us because transformation
is the key to survive and to be
successful. Okay. And one thing is that
transformation actually will give us the
opportunity to stay relevant. And this
morning when our CEO Kelvin mentioned
about Nokia is resonated with me very
very deeply about transformation. You
guys remember why Nokia failed in the
mobile industry? Because it's not about
lacking of resources but because Nokia
did not adapt to the change fast enough
in the market. So if us as agent we do
not transform, we do not evolve. We do
not stay relevant in the business.
Basically the our clients needs will not
be well taken care of. Remember one
thing, you are the advisor for your
client's needs and for your client's
goal. Not just for today but for
tomorrow and not just for the one
generation but for multiple generations.
potency
for energy and kaka the web's
transformation and growth are so
meaningful to kick off the new year
class agency force growing stronger and
better and be the undisputed number one
in the industry
>> absolutely moving. Now you might be
thinking why focus on consumer segment?
Aren't they just a small segment? Yes,
you're right. Making this shows that
there only 6% of Malaysian household are
belong to consumer segment. But here is
the questions. How much premium growth
do you expect this statement can bring
over the next 3 years? Any guesses?
>> 20%.
No, it's more than that actually. Let me
review is 54% growth over the next 3
years. So this has certainly make this a
must win segment for driving our
business forward. And now we have seen
this immense opportunity. It's important
for us to understand what's their needs
and how what are they really looking
for. Are you here 5,000 well members and
many more out there. We need to shift
from transitional styling to holistic
needing and this how we can win big in
the space. T you have any addons?
You have covered it very well and now
let's hear from our leaders.
Special
set.
Okay.
Privacy
service
exclusive.
human interaction
and let's hear from Kaka how usually you
approach the affluent customer. Thank
you Sing. For myself actually when it
comes to affluent market I have
literally three. My affluent market
consist of three different segment. The
first segment is business owners. Second
segment is uh professionals like a
doctors and the last segment is a high
netw worth individuals. I think most of
us as a adviser, we always want to work
with business owner because we always
have the um thoughts that business
owners are the ones that have the law of
wealth and we are there for them to
manage the wealth. But now the question
is that you want to tap into the
business owners market. You must
understand how to have a meaningful
conversation with them. So that's why
that actually today I'm going to share a
little bit key words that you can
actually share with the business owner.
There's one thing I would like to
actually speak to business owner which
is talk about cash flow. So I identify
this is that every business owner can
always have a cash flow uh blind spot.
And why I say this is that statistic
shows that 91% of the business owner
fails when they actually face the
financial difficulty. Do you know why?
Because they do not have a liquidity.
Guys remember this 91% of the business
owner are rich in assets but they are
very poor in cash flow. So when they are
poor in cash flow what happen they will
find they will face a financial
difficulty. So you don't actually only
mention about income replacement or
income protection because to begin with
business owner don't care about income
they only care about their profit and
their risk taker. So you must understand
the choice of what you need to speak to
business owner. So you talk about cash
flow, cash flow balance. Then they
understand okay something happened to me
I need cash flow and you know that as a
matter of fact you do not have any cash
flow when we face financial difficulty
and we are the one will be there to
provide liquidity for you and there's no
other liquidity as powerful as
insurance. That's why we as the advisor
we have to reach out to business owner
and identify their cash flow blind spot.
Okay. The second one which is doctor
professionals. Most of us when it comes
to um FIC doctors, we always focus on
income protection and I call it as a
professional uh uh pro professional uh
income protections for the professionals
which is a doctor's but most of us we
only stop at their income which is
doctor's income. I always call it as a
professional protection planning. But
think about it, we can always go beyond
that. We can always go about the
business sustainability or business
continuation for the doctors. Because
most of the doctors, they have a
external clinic outside. If something
happened to them, what happened to their
patient? What happened to their nurses?
What happened to their business? What
happened to their clinic? So all the
coverage that actually they buy from
your CI coverage is go beyond their
income only. But you have to go to their
business continuation. That is the
second um topic which is the
professionals. And the last is not least
which is high net worth individuals.
When it comes to high net worth
individuals they don't talk about wealth
because they have so much wealth and
high net worth individuals they only
focus on two things which is the first
wealth preservation and the second is
that income preservation. They don't
talk about wealth accumulation because
they have accumulated enough wealth. But
what is in their mind is that how am I
going to pass down my wealth? Can my
children actually manage the wealth and
can my wealth last for multiple
generations? That is the concern that
most of my client have when they buy a
high summer machine for me. So I'm very
happy about today because something is
coming up and actually will address our
client who have buy who have actually
bought high submission from us. Thank
you. True enhancement designed to
deliver even greater value and security.
We have enhanced the SL death benefits.
They have now included a top selling
critical insurance rider TMCC as part of
the growth. But I also want to share
more about the new legacy settlement
option which is the most flexible option
in car today
because say wealth doesn't last beyond
3D generation Chinese saying
the segment will resist the most like
what kaga has mentioned that's why has
created a smarter way for your client or
customer to manage their legacy with
legacy set options customer can decide
when, how, and how much to distribute
their wealth either as a lump sum or a
structured installment for up to 35
years or true milestone payout for the
child graduations, marriage or even when
you start a new business. And the best
part is it's offered at no extra cost
and this will be made available on 11th
January.
Okay, let's play a short video to
showcase this legacy.
>> Ever since I started a family, my life
is more than just me.
Every decision I make now is for them.
I always try to make sure their path is
a little easier than mine. every step of
the way.
The decisions I make today
will shape my daughter's [music] future.
It gives me wealth distribution tailored
to my family's living needs [music]
protection from misuse to ensure what I
leave is used wisely
and interest that may acrue on any
remaining balance helping my legacy
grow. [music]
And it reaches them in ways that matter.
[music] An immediate lump sum for
pressing financial needs. [music]
Installment for up to 35 years
or
milestone based payouts for life's
[music] most meaningful moments.
And with every payout comes a personal
[music] message.
my words,
my guidance.
So they feel my presence [music] at
every milestone.
Legacy is more than wealth.
It's care,
intention,
and love that endures long after you're
gone. [music]
Legacy settlement option. Let your love
live on into the next generation.
>> We just want to make sure that they
leave enough money for the next
generations. I think most of us as
advisor we always think of that how much
money do you want to leave behind but
when it comes to legacy planning the
true meaning behind legacy plannings is
beyond how much that's why that I start
with the four questions that I will
share with all of you and please
practice this immediately tomorrow like
what mentioned tomorrow we have to kick
start ourselves and everything so most
of us we always talk about the first
question which How much should be left
behind? That is most advisor will do
that. Okay, how much sh 5 million, 10
million? That's it. But you have to
understand that is is more like is that
the money that you're going to leave
behind whether is sufficient or not.
That is where insurance come into the
picture. From the small money make into
the big money, right? That's how
insurance works. But we don't ever
forget to move to the second question
which is how will the asset be
contributed or distributed to the next
generations. Do you want to be lump pay
out? Do you want to be staggered pay out
or do you want to have a structure that
pay over time? I think the word of
structure is very important because we
as agent we focus too much on product.
We have to go beyond product and move
into structure. Okay. That's how they
asset be distributed. You want how
structure can be done in what they want
to do. The third question how and when
do the beneficiary receive the wealth. I
think this is very important because
some of the parents which is a high
level family as well they want to make
sure that certain wealth they want the
children to receive at what age the
first second milestone the third
probably during marriage or the last
probably during the business set up.
Some of my client they want to make sure
that the the children already listen to
money when they have a grandchildren.
Yeah. So this is the next question we as
investor must understand and must give
the right solution. And last not least
which is how will the wealth be managed
and protected either the third party or
what actually we can do now is that our
LSO the the settlement options is very
very powerful. So when I heard that
there's this announcement is really
really I'm very happy I'm very excited
to share my trial because this is
something that my client is looking for
which is something that they want to
preserve for multiple generation and not
only for one generations. So we have to
actually detect our adviser not only
serve one generation but we have to
serve multiple generations
in premium and contribution and at the
same time we also notice that CI is
increasing in Malaysia at credential the
total CI payout has been increased
significantly by 59%
over the past three years for 2 years
the total CI pay out has doubled over
the last three years. This reflect one
thing that is people now have higher
awareness over critical illness coverage
and they place priority to it. We also
notice that the open statement shows a
higher CI attachment as compared to the
mass segment by 10%. And policy or
certificate the CI attached to it tends
to have higher case size by 15%. Ladies
and gentlemen, what does all this tell
us? It means that CI solution has great
market opportunity and this is one way
we can capture the affluent customers.
Speaking about capturing sales. Every
one of you, you are the expert and every
one of you, you sure have your own
marketing concept for the way how you
position a CI product. But let's hear
from our leader. Let me ask Jojo.
Okay.
business.
business plan.
The business owner in replace
Big
business.
Okay.
Killer sentence.
district continuation plan
and today I have good news for all of
you
products.
>> [music]
>> 360
market
number one.
We want to go
first in the market.
virtually
insurance. Remember daddy customers
personalized services
value added services.
Are you excited about this new product?
Are you excited?
[music]
Foreign
speech. Foreign speech. Foreign speech.
for
[music]
you by the clock, please.
>> [music]
>> blessings.
I think guys keep this in mind. Peace of
mind is nonnegotiable.
Okay, that's our job to give peace of
mind to our client. So peace of mind
must be non-negotiable
and that only happen when you work with
us as an insurance advisor because we
great uncertainty become certain. And
one last thing before I end my slide is
that remember the true impact is not
measured by how much you sell but how
many family that you protected and how
many conflicts you prevent and how how
much value you preserve and don't sell
policy build legacies.
How are you? Okay.
Thank you for the great show today and
please give them a big hand.